anabolic.com 2004-06-10

# Anabolic Video Productions - Legal Information

**Privacy Policy**

**Our Commitment To Privacy**   
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

When applying for a membership to "members-only" areas of AnabolicXXX.com, your personal information is collected by [CCBILL](http://www.ccbill.com/). Please see their Privacy Policy concerning collected information. For customer support purposes, [CCBILL](http://www.ccbill.com/) may make some of your personal information (this is limited to your name, address, phone number, e-mail, and payment method only) available to us. **We do not share your personal information with ANY third parties.**

When renting DivX rental movies on Anabolic.com at [http://www.Anabolic.com/divx/](http://www.anabolic.com/divx/), your personal information is collected by [IBILL](http://www.ibill.com/). Please see their Privacy Policy concerning collected information. For customer support purposes, IBILL may make some of your personal information (this is limited to your name, address, phone number, e-mail, and payment method only) available to us. **We do not share your personal information with ANY third parties.**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on Diabolic Video Production, Inc.'s DiabolicXXX.com website. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**   
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**   
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us using the methods described below. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us**   
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at **[webmaster@anabolic.com](mailto:webmaster@anabolic.com)**
